環球影片公司
相對論傳媒
聯合制作
藍草影業
製作
丹澤爾·華盛頓
瑞恩· 雷諾茲
藏身之所
今天我要和派克說說升職的事
I'm going to talk to Parker about my promotion today.
最遲兩個星期後跟你會合
In the worst-case scenario you're two weeks ahead of me,
瑪黑區: 巴黎著名的同性戀聚集地
你可以先住在瑪黑區漂亮的小公寓
you get a gorgeous little apartment in the Marais.
那如果我不喜歡瑪黑區呢
What if I don't want to live in the Marais?
那我們就住別的地方
We could live somewhere else, then.
-真的嗎  -當然
- Yeah? - Yeah.
我們可以去底特律
We could go to Detroit.
底特律
Detroit?
對  順便見見我的父母
Yeah, you could meet my mom and dad.
還有我的妹妹  她有一家烘焙作坊
You can meet my sister. She owns a bakery,
一定能把你養得又白又胖
and she will make you fat.
我再過六個鐘頭才回醫院
I have six hours before I have to go back to the hospital.
想不想滾床單呀
You want to go back into bed with me?
樂意至極
I do.
可惜我上午的行程滿滿當當的
But I got back-to-back meetings all morning.
真可惜
Too bad for you.
是啊
Yeah, I know.
我該走了
But I got to get in.
大概有25個人
There's probably already 25 people
排隊在外面等著了
lined up outside the door, waiting.
你說法語時真迷人
I love when you speak French.
身份確認
Satcom check.
編號E93VE2
Echo Nine Three Victor Echo Two.
管理中心
Ops Center.
這裡是7-R安全屋  正常營業
This is safe house 7-R. We're open for business.
確認
Confirmed.
有預約嗎
Any reservations?
沒有預約
Nothing in the registry.
即時業務呢
Walk-ins?
沒有  3小時後重新確認
Not expected. Reconfirm in three hours.
明白
Understood.
星期四
下午1:53
馬特嗎  你怎麼能打給我
Matt? Your cell, really?
放心  號碼加密了
Relax, l've got an encryption packet.
你瞭解我  我一直很警惕
You know me, I never relax.
小心三高  老頭
Watch the cholesterol, old man.
怎麼跟米里亞姆一個腔調
You sound like Miriam.
開普敦有消息嗎
So, what's new in Cape Town?
沒什麼
Nothing, nothing.
我升級了監視分析系統  報告已經完成了
I updated my Surveillance Target Analysis. It's complete now.
那個報告  等你調離的時候才算完成
Yeah, that's an exit report. It's not due until you leave.
是的  那什麼時候調我走啊
Exactly. Exactly. And when is that?
待多久了
How long has it been?
整整12個月
Twelve months.
再過4個月再說
Well, talk to me in another four.
大衛  我都要閑死了
David, I'm dying here.
巴黎那邊的職位怎麼樣了
What's happening with the post in Paris?
1個位置  37個人搶
One slot, 37 applicants.
每個人都比你經驗豐富
Every one of them with more field experience than you.
我成日盯著四面牆
How am I supposed to get more experience?
哪來的經驗
I'm staring at four walls all day.
先是羅馬那邊拒絕了我  再來是柏林
I got passed up on Rome, then Berlin.
是你說的  我的評估很出色
You said yourseLf, my evaluation was excellent.
只要把報告交給魏特福
Just put it in front of Whitford.
他就能把我調走  這是我全部心血
I know he'll see that l'm ready to go, I'm all in.
馬特  我知道你不好過
Matt, I know this has been hard,
但還是得照著程式走
but it's the way the system works.
我會和魏特福談談巴黎那邊的職位
Look, I'll talk to Whitford about Paris,
但我不能保證有結果
but I can't promise anything.
我該掛了
Look, I've got to go.
別擔心  我罩著你呢
Don't worry, I'm looking after you, okay?
好  我明白  我明白
Yeah, I know, I know, I know.
一口價
This is not a negotiation.
一千萬拿來
It's 10 million.
文件就給你
You'll get the file, and if the money
下午3點前沒到賬
is not in the account by 3:00 P.M. ,
我就另謀買主了
I'll take it to another buyer.
我們怎麼知道你的檔沒有賣給別人過
How do we know that you won't do that anyway?
你說呢
You don't.
這邊  先生
Here you are, sir.
埃裡克  近來可好
Alec, how are you?
柏圖斯莊園: 是當今世界上公認的頂級紅酒區
柏圖斯莊園  年份1972
Petrus, 1972.
你春風得意啊
You look good.
那是自然
I do, don't I?
軍情六處那邊怎麼樣了
So, how are things at MI6?
老樣子  打打官腔領點薪水
The usual. Same bureaucratic bullshit and appalling remuneration.
典型的政府公務員
Life of a government man.
文件呢
So. . .
原始檔
The original file.
日期  交易  名單
Dates, transactions, names.
三合一優惠價
A bargain at triple the price.
打開看看
Take a look.
這一天我等很久了
I've been waiting a long time for this.
托賓
Tobin. . .
盒子裡的東西
What's in that box is going to make
會讓這個世界變小
the world a smaller place for you,
容不下你我二人
for both of us.
你的帳戶
I got your account.
24小時後將收到匯款
You get your cut 24 hours after transaction.
這些資料洩露出去
Some of our old bosses aren't going to be happy
我們的老上司不會太高興
these files are out in the open.
我讓你不自在了嗎
Do I make you nervous?
-一直  -好極了
- Always. - Good.
想上她
You want her?
請聽我說
Please, listen to me.
我對此一無所知
I had nothing to do with this.
停
Stop.
走吧
Let's go.
托賓  請務必相信我
Tobin, you have to believe me.
我真的不知情
I knew nothing about any of that.
有人在跟蹤你嗎
Did you know if anybody was following you?
不  應該沒有
No, I don't think anybody was following me.
我發誓  托賓  我絕對...
I swear on my life, Tobin, I had absolutely...
慢點
Slow down.
我們下車走
We're going by foot.
廣場方向
Head towards the square.
快  快  快
Move! Move! Move!
我們正往西邊走
We're heading west.
荷蘭路  快
Holland Street. Move, move.
美利堅合眾國總領事館
稍等  先生  謝謝
Excuse me, sir. Thank you.
我是托賓·福斯特
My name is Tobin Frost.
維吉尼亞州蘭利  中情局總部
林克雷特
Linklater.
什麼時候
When?
封閉領事館
Lock down the consulate.
5分鐘內組織一批人到情報室
Get me a team in the Situation Room in five minutes.
動用一切資源  盯緊托賓·福斯特
I want everything we got on Tobin Frost.
遵命  長官
Yes, ma'am.
-是他嗎  -是的
- Is it him? - Yep.
魏特福知道嗎
Whitford know?
我正趕往那裡
I'm on my way there now.
先生  請把您的手指放在上面
Sir, place your finger in there until I tell you to stop.
謝謝
Thank you.
他在你的地方多久了
So how long has he been playing in your backyard?
我們正在調查
We're working to get you that answer right now.
意思是  你不知道
Meaning you don't know.
意思是  我們正在調查
No, meaning, we're looking into it.
這傢伙  他9年內
The guy goes rogue, he spends nine years
向任何你想得到的國家
selling out the Agency to all takers.
俄羅斯  中國  伊朗販賣組織情報
To Russia, China, Iran, you name it.
他就這麼大搖大擺地進美國領事館
The guy is just not going to prance
恐怕另有企圖
into an American consulate without good reason.
好了  聽著
All right, listen up.
大家放下手中的活
Everybody off the phone.
托賓·福斯特方才闖進
Tobin Frost has just waltzed his way
我國在南非開普敦的領事館
into a U.S. Consulate in Cape Town, South Africa.
毫無疑問  這個人
Now this man, without question,
是迄今最為臭名昭著的交易人
is one of the most notorious traders that we've got.
厄靈頓  調出他的背景資料
Errington, call up his background profile.
托賓·福斯特於1984年加入中情局
Tobin Frost was recruited into the Agency in 1984.
在心理學領域
He tested off the charts
具有極高造詣
in aptitude for psychological field work.
他第一個任務是1985年1月  在黎巴嫩
His first assignment was in Lebanon, in January, 1985.
3個月後  他抓住真主党的高級領袖
Three months later, he captured and flipped
真主党: 是1982年黎巴嫩人為了抵抗以色列入侵  成立的什葉派伊斯蘭政治和軍事組織
並套出大量資訊
a high-ranking Hezbollah leader.
在接下來的幾年中
Over the next several years,
福斯特成功審查網羅了
Frost successfully questioned
多名極有價值的人才
and recruited many high-value individuals.
他在情報審控領域名稱彰於世
He became known as an expert manipulator of human assets,
幾乎是重寫了情報審問的歷史
and he literally rewrote Agency interrogation protocols.
福斯特曾效力於多個活動組織
Frost served in many active theaters,
包括1995到1998年  在利比亞
including Libya from 1995 to 1998,
1998到2000年  在約旦
Jordan, 1998 to 2000.
在約旦的在任期間
During his tenure in Jordan,
摩薩德: 全稱為以色列情報和特殊使命局  世界三大情報組織之一
福斯特被指控向摩薩德洩露資訊
Frost was suspected of leaking information to Mossad,
但無證據證明
but nothing was confirmed.
10年前  福斯特徹底脫離組織
Ten years ago, Frost went off the reservation completely.
目前並未向任何人效力
He currently has no allegiances
現今在四大洲遭間諜罪通緝
and is wanted for espionage on four continents.
最後一次現身是2011年在德國漢堡
His last known sighting is Hamburg, Germany, in 2011 .
哈倫  我們該審問福斯特了
You know, Harlan, we should interrogate Frost now.
榨幹他身上所有資訊
Sweat him for everything he's got.
一旦他登陸美國  我們就束手無策了
Once he's stateside, we have fewer options.
我在葉門有審問員  8個小時能到
I have an interrogator in Yemen, can be there in eight hours.
我在約翰尼斯堡有人手  兩個小時能到
I already have a team in Jo'burg that can be there in two.
我們現在就帶福斯特前往安全屋受審
We'll take Frost to the safe house, interrogate him there.
我的手下完全可以應付
My people are fully capable of handling this.
這可是托賓·福斯特
This is Tobin Frost.
調約翰尼斯堡的人吧
We'll go with Jo'burg.
好吧
Okay.
你早晚會出頭
You must turn around.
幫幫忙
Help. Help.
來點事幹
Accident.
客房服務
Housekeeping.
我們有緊急預約
We have a last-minute reservation.
何時入住
ETA for check-in?
晚些時候  自由方舟保險公司
Sometime tonight. Freeark Insurance.
明白
Got it.
-喂  -喂
- Hello. - Hey.
你在哪兒
Hey, where are you?
派克剛把他的文件丟給我做
Parker just handed me his oversight papers to finish
沒成想他的女兒克洛伊得了麻疹
and his daughter Chloe's got the measles, can you believe that?
你幾點回去
How long are you going to be out for?
不知道  不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
好  我先把這事忙活完
Okay. Well, look, I'm gonna dive into this,
希望晚點能和你見面  好嗎
and then hopefully I can meet up with you later, okay?
好的  晚點見
Yeah, that sounds good.
我愛你
I love you.
我也愛你
I love you, too.
-再見  -再見
- Bye. - Bye.
約翰尼斯堡  斯瓦特克博空軍基地
審問隊已經在路上  長官
Extraction team is in the air, sir.
1小時內就能抵達
They should be on the ground within the hour.
這支隊伍要在12小時內完成任務離開
I want that team in and out of the city in less than 12 hours.
不能讓人發現出現在開普敦
We're not even supposed to have a presence in Cape Town.
是  長官
Yes, sir.
任何有關福斯特的行蹤情報
Any communications about
須立即上報
Frost's whereabouts are strictly need-to-know.
長官  審問隊在前往領事館的路上
Sir, the extraction team is on route to the consulate now.
誰與7-R聯繫的
Who's reaching out to 7-R?
理查  長官
Richards, ma'am.
告知看守
I want the housekeeper briefed.
重要目標移入  務必清出閒雜人等
High-priority target is coming in. I want the house quiet.
審問人員離開之前
Under no circumstances should there be
決不允許走漏任何風聲
any communication until the team has left.
是  長官
Yes, ma'am.
安全級別四級  移入高危險人物
務必謹慎
時刻保持兩米間隔
啟動四級安全防護
目標極具攻擊性  執行全套防護措施
星期五
淩晨5:37
有事嗎
Yeah?
還有房間嗎
Do you have a room?
-姓名  -丹尼爾·季福爾
- Account? - Daniel Kiefer.
自由方舟保險公司  季-福-爾
Freeark lnsurance. K-l-E-F-E-R.
季福爾  自由方舟保險公司  季-福-爾
Kiefer. Freeark Insurance. K-l-E-F-E-R.
讓他進來
You are a go.
你可以進來了
You're good to go.
-你好  我是韋斯頓  -審問室呢
- Hi, l'm Weston. - Guest room?
在拐角處  右轉兩次後左轉
It's right around the corner. Two rights and a left.
一直朝前走
All the way back.
那是托賓·福斯特
That's Tobin Frost.
守著他  去準備器材吧
Stay with him. Let's go download our gear.
是  長官
Yes, sir.
毛巾櫃在哪兒
Linen closet?
在大廳  往前直走到底
Down the hall. Just right at the end, there.
關掉這房間的所有攝像頭
Kill all the surveillance cameras in this room.
我是丹尼爾·季福爾
My name is Daniel Kiefer.
農場: 佩里營的綽號  美國中央情報局的訓練營  位於維吉尼亞州約克縣
我們一起在農場幹過
We were at The Farm together.
準確地說  你比我早去一年
Technically, you were a year ahead.
我來告知你的權益
I'm here to make you aware of your rights.
你被以國家安全條例羈押
You're being held under a National Security Directive,
也就是說  沒有人權  這你心知肚明
which means you have none, but you know that.
Six-hundreds.
這樣的毛巾  你要用600克的
The towels, you need six-hundreds.
這種毛巾重350到375克
Those are 350, 375-gram weight.
你需要600克的
You're gonna need six-hundreds.
我要知道你來開普敦的原因
I want to know the reasons for you being in Cape Town.
我要你報上情報資源  聯絡方式  人手
I want you to name your resources, contacts, assets,
以及從你叛國開始的9年間
everybody you've done business with,
和誰做交易
traded intel with, sold secrets to,
買賣情報機密
in the nine years since you betrayed your country.
當然  如你所願  丹尼爾
Absolutely. Anything you want, Daniel.
哈立德·謝赫·穆罕默德: 恐怖組織成員  涉嫌包括911在內的多起恐怖襲擊案件
哈立德·謝赫·穆罕默德堅持了20秒
Khalid Sheikh Mohammed lasted 20 seconds.
他們用了600克的
They had six-hundreds.
這合法嗎
Is this legal?
按下去
Bring him down.
拉起來
Bring him up.
我堅持了多久
How long was that?
好極了  再按下去
All right, take him down.
拉起來
Bring him up!
給我把刀
Get me a knife.
米勒
Miller?
進去看著福斯特
Get in there with Frost.
長官  所有的監控都關了
Sir, all the security cameras are down.
-重啟  看看外面怎麼了  -是
- Reboot. I want to see what's out there. - Copy that.
快走  兄弟們
Let's go, boys!
快走  快走
Go! Go! Go!
快  快走
Let's go, move!
威萊斯  守著這裡
Velez, take this corner.
埃裡克森  去暗梯
Ericksson, get the back elevator.
波普  情況如何
Pope, what do you got?
長官  方圓兩米內約有12名武裝分子
Sir, l see approximately 12 heavily armed men in perimeter two.
好了  從前往後
Okay, gents! Work fore to aft.
兩米內  兩兩搭檔
Two-by-twos. Perimeter two.
-蓋賴爾  -長官
- Greer? - Sir!
-埃裡克森  -是  長官
- Ericksson? - Yes, sir.
威萊斯
Velez?
我沒事
I'm good !
準備  兄弟們
Let's go, fellas.
-敵方突襲  -手榴彈
- Incoming ! - Grenade!
蓋賴爾
Greer!
分兩邊  撤退
Step-slide! Start walking back!
威萊斯  三輪爆炸
Velez! Three-round bursts!
威萊斯  蓋賴爾在哪兒
Velez, where's Greer?
他在那兒  長官
He's over there, sir.
上吧  孩子
Go, son.
不是演習  這是來真的
This ain't a test. This is the real thing.
你作何打算
What are you gonna do?
少激我
You don't want to try me.
-彈藥  -走
- Magazine! - Let's go.
威萊斯  別動
Velez, stay there!
聽著  別動
Listen to me, stay there!
狗娘養的
Son of a bitch !
米勒
Miller!
進來
Get in here!
拿著
Take these.
看住他
Go watch him.
他們是沖著我來的  但他們得留我活口
They're here for me, but they want me alive.
而你  性命堪憂
You, they'll kill.
還有子彈嗎
You got one in the chamber?
沒關係
It's okay.
我還記得我第一個任務  在里約熱內盧
I remember my first posting. Rio de Janeiro.
像這樣的屋子  美女如雲
A house like this. Beautiful women.
沒有任何訪客  但記住首要法則
Not one single visitor, but I remember rule number one.
你要對來客負責
You are responsible for your houseguest.
你要對我負責
I'm your houseguest.
時間在流逝  他們給了你鑰匙
The clock is ticking. They gave you the keys.
幹你該幹的事  老弟
Do your duty, son.
閉嘴  讓我想想
Shut up. Let me think.
你想成為丟了托賓·福斯特的眾矢之的嗎
You want to be the guy that lost Tobin Frost?
要沒時間了呦
Tick-tock, tick-tock, tick-tock.
福斯特在哪
Where's Frost?
我們撤
We're leaving.
他在哪兒
Where is he?
星期五
早上8:17
待在這兒  等著  別動
Stay here, stay here! Wait! Don't move!
走
Go!
進後備箱
Get in the trunk.
-別開玩笑  -不開玩笑  進去
- Are you serious? - Yeah, get in.
-後備箱  -進去  現在
- The trunk? - Get in the trunk now!
靠
No!
管理中心
Ops Center.
編號E3VE9
Echo Three Victor Echo Nine.
說吧
Go ahead.
我是韋斯頓  7-R被襲擊了
This is Weston. 7-R's been hit.
全員遇難
Everyone's dead.
請重複  請重複
I need you to repeat that, please. Say again.
季福爾和他的手下  全部遇難
Kiefer, his team, everyone, they're all dead.
請稍等
Stand by.
轉接中
Transferring.
是安全屋
lt's the house.
-林克雷特  -我是韋斯頓
- Linklater. - This is Weston.
安全屋被襲擊了
The safe house has been breached.
現處位置
What's your location?
我正沿亞伯特路的東向開
I'm eastbound on Albert Road.
剛路過伍斯托克
I'm just passing woodstock.
盯著他們  即時報告
I want eyes on this. Real-time sat feed.
房客在哪兒
And what's the location of the guest?
我們逃出來了
We escaped.
重複  房客在你旁邊嗎
Clarify. Do you have the guest?
對  我們逃出來了
Yes, we escaped !
聽著  我可以到領事館去
Look, I can make it to the consulate.
無法使用無線電
There's no chance for SDR,
我被跟了
I think I might have picked up a tail.
我們可不能在領事館前發生槍戰
We can't have a gun battle in front of the consulate.
外交災難
Diplomatic catastrophe.
衛星監視呢
Where's that satellite feed?
被國家偵察局切斷了  只能在戰爭時啟用
Denied by National Recon. War theater use only.
拖住他們
Buy us some time.
不要去領事館
Do not go to the consulate.
謹記首要法則
Follow protocol Alpha Zero.
保護證人  甩掉敵方
Secure the guest and stay off the grid.
晚6點聯絡
Reconnect at 1800 hours.
再說一次  甩掉敵方
I repeat, stay off the grid.
明白  明白  明白
Copy, copy, copy.
開普敦的警方正在處理安全屋
All right, Cape Town police have responded to the house.
-確認  -封鎖安全屋
- Confirmed. - I want the site secured.
已有9人死亡
I'm hearing nine dead.
盡力減少損失
Initiating damage control.
正在處理  正在接通國家情報局
I'm on it. Reaching out to NIA now.
當地將封鎖安全屋
The locals are going to have that house locked off.
核對所有的交通監控  警方報告
Check all the traffic cameras, police reports...
弄清福斯特進入領事館的原因
Find out why Frost wanted to go in that consulate to begin with
和追殺他的人的情況
and who in the hell else might be after him.
我們得把韋斯頓和福斯特弄出南非
We need to get Weston and Frost out of South Africa.
我們有應對小組嗎  採取措施了嗎
Now, do we have any tactical teams? Anything in play?
我在埃及有隊伍  但他們正在潛伏
Yeah, l have assets in Egypt, but they're in deep.
如果我調離他們
If I pull them out,
兩年的努力就白費了
that would compromise two years' worth of work.
我能從歐洲或亞洲抽1支隊伍出來
I can scramble a team from Europe or Asia,
但至少要花18個小時
but it's going to take at least 18 hours.
現在我們只能從韋斯頓下手
At this point, Weston is all we got.
立刻搞清馬特·韋斯頓是誰
I need to find out who this Matt Weston is, right now.
馬特·詹姆斯·韋斯頓
Matthew James Weston.
生於82年2月24日  父母為泰瑞和瑪德琳·韋斯頓
Born 02-24-82 to Terry and Madeline Weston
出生地  紐約華盛頓港
in Port washington, New York.
曾因傷害罪被捕
An assault arrest, one month after
之前一個月其父母及妹妹因車禍喪生
both parents and a younger sister were killed in a traffic accident
車禍原因為
in which his father's blood-alcohol
其父醉酒駕駛
was twice the legal limit.
耶魯大學畢業  經濟學專業  破格錄取
Yale, degree in Economics, recruited out of Yale law.
在斯坦福大學時  分析學和語言學獲得高分
High marks in analytics and linguistics at The Farm.
具有極好的諜報技巧
Excellent in tradecraft skills.
他的女朋友  安娜·莫羅  法國人
His girlfriend, Ana Moreau, is a French national.
他的報告上說  他們有"親密且持續的接觸"
He reported them as having "Close and continuing contact."
她是第二年常駐醫生
She's a second year resident
專攻腫瘤學  格魯特·舒爾醫院
in the oncology department at Groote Schuur.
進那輛車
Get in that car.
她接受了何特爾·迪沃醫院的職位
She accepted a position with Hotel-Dieu Hospital
兩周後動身去巴黎
in Paris, starts in two weeks.
無黨派人士  也沒有案底
No known political affiliations. She's clean.
派一輛車監視他們的公寓
I want you to post a car outside their apartment.
內線聯繫
Use back channels.
聯繫安全局
And get NSA to cross-check
對比他們的通話記錄和電郵
their telephone records and their e-mails, please.
好的  長官
Yes, ma'am.
星期五
下午1:13
你要是告訴我目的地會方便點
You know, it would be easier if I knew where we were going.
開你的車  中間車道
You just drive, all right? Just drive, middle lane.
好吧
All right.
你幹什麼  中間車道
Hey, what are you doing? Middle lane.
開就行了
Just drive around.
好  我在開
All right. I'm driving.
知道自己在和誰說話比較好  你叫什麼
Nice to know who you're talking to. What's your name?
你差點把我勒死
You crushed my windpipe.
你先把我鎖到後備箱裡的
Well, you locked me in the trunk.
你不是臥底  用的是真名
Come on, you're not NOC. You're here under your real name.
叫什麼
What is it?
馬特·韋斯頓
Weston, Matt.
好的
All right.
你當安全屋看守多久了
How long you been a safe house keeper?
12個月
Twelve months.
周年快樂啊
Happy birthday.
開普敦不算什麼機密
Cape Town, that's low-level detail.
你現在應該自由了
You should have been out of here by now.
也許我有新任務了呢
Maybe I requested the assignment.
也許情報局不再信任你了
Or maybe Langley doesn't trust you with anything else.
你有什麼計畫
So, what's your plan?
讓我來猜猜  你打算根據法則行事
Oh, let me guess. Follow protocol.
根據法則如果你的安全屋暴露了
Protocol states that if your house is crashed,
先用反追蹤技能確保無人跟蹤
you do an SDR to make sure no one's following you.
使用應急包裡的定位系統  選擇一個新安全屋
Activate your GPS in your Go-Bag, select another safe house.
你以為我會讓你把我關起來嗎
You think I'm going to let you just take me in?
你給我閉嘴
I think you need to shut up.
你應該先想想
I think you need to consider
為什麼你的安全屋會被攻擊
how your house was attacked in the first place.
你考慮過嗎  馬特
Have you done that, Matt?
他們跟蹤季福爾  從領事館一直跟過來
They followed Kiefer. They followed him from the consulate,
然後找到了安全屋
and that's how they found the safe house.
得了吧  你不會真這麼想吧
Come on, you don't really believe that, do you?
他們怎麼事先料到我會在領事館附近
How did they know l was near the consulate in the first place?
我喜歡這樣  我們倆一起思考問題
But l like this, you know. You and me, figuring shit out.
就像硬漢兄弟一樣
Like the Hardy Boys.
那間安全屋很隱秘
That house was a secure location.
那些追殺者
Whoever crashed it
肯定不會停在加油站
didn't stop by a gas station
問出最近的安全屋在哪
and ask for directions to the nearest safe house.
他們是被招引過來的  有人告密了  馬特
They were invited. Someone told them, Matthew.
仔細想想  你認識的人
Think about it. Someone you know.
你得好好問自己  你能信任自己的上司嗎
So you better ask yourself, can you trust your landlord?
算了吧  我不會聽你挑撥的
Go ahead, you're not going to get in my head.
你已經開始懷疑了
I already am in your head.
他們在孤立你  馬特
They're going to isolate you, Matt.
一開始他們會對你很好
They're going to be real nice to you at first.
胳膊搭在你肩膀上
They're going to put their
一邊這麼跟你說
arm around you and tell you things like,
"你幹得不錯  下面我們接手"
"You did a decent job, son. We'll take it from here."
那時候你就知道自己完蛋了
That's when you know you're screwed.
別考慮我  他們的目標是你
Forget about me. They're going to focus on you.
他們會試圖讓你我之間有關聯
They're going to try and make a connection between you and I.
這樣如果計畫失敗
So that if this all goes wrong,
在最後參議院聽證會時
they'll have something to fall back on
他們就有墊背了
in their little Senate hearings.
今晚我不是你唯一的敵人
I'm not your only enemy tonight.
有內鬼
So, it's someone in-house.
只可能是這樣
It's the only way this thing could've happened.
我們完全被蒙蔽了
We were completely buttoned up.
給我所有知道行動的人的名單
I want a list of everyone who knew about this.
背景  從屬關係
Backgrounds, affiliations,
尤其是任何與福斯特的聯繫
particularly any connections with Frost.
這次計畫前的每一次行動
Every movement right up until this operation.
你的審問隊  組隊多久了
Your extraction team, how long had they been together?
組隊6個月  怎麼了
My team had been together six months. Why?
我只是想把事情搞清楚
Well, I'm just trying to get my head around this.
你們可以走了  謝謝
That will do, thank you.
-情報呢  -情報丟失
-可以找回嗎  -可以
沒有情報就沒有報酬
明白
斯坦德酒店  巴羅  開普敦西側
-喂  -是我
- Hello. - Hey.
寶貝  你在哪
Baby, where are you?
我很好  我沒事
I'm all right. I'm okay.
我沒事
I'm okay.
對不起沒回你電話  我看到未接來電了
I'm sorry I didn't call you back, I saw your missed calls.
你肯定擔心死了
You must be worried sick.
都順利嗎
Is everything okay?
我很好  聽著
I'm good. I'm good. Listen.
這聽起來很瘋狂
This sounds so crazy.
昨晚診所被襲擊了
We had some threats against the clinic last night,
所以派克和我
so Parker and I, we stayed all night
整晚都在弄清怎麼回事
trying to get to the bottom of it.
對不起沒有回你電話
And I'm sorry that I didn't call you back.
我應該立刻回復的
I should have, right away.
我真的好擔心
I was so worried.
我知道
I know.
能幫我個忙嗎
Can you do me a favor?
你能到窗戶那去一下嗎
Can you go over to the window for a second?
怎麼了
why?
你能瞄一眼外面嗎
Can you just take a quick look out the window?
我想讓你看看有沒有人
I want you to see if there's anyone out there.
有沒有陌生的車
Are there any cars that don't belong?
有沒有徘徊不走的人
Anyone hanging around out front?
有輛警車
There's a police car.
發生什麼事了
What's going on?
真的對不起
I'm sorry about this.
我知道這很過分
I know this is a lot,
但是為了以防萬一
but we felt like it would be best
我們最好不要回家
if we didn't go home as a precaution,
我也這麼覺得
and I agree with him.
雖然沒什麼好擔心的  但是這樣最好
I know there's nothing to worry about, but I agree with him.
你該去黛娜家避一避
I think you should just go to Dena's for a little while,
就幾個小時  我一會兒打給你
just for a few hours, and I'll call you in a little bit.
然後我們碰面  好嗎
And we'll get together, okay?
好  我會去的
Okay, I'll go.
我愛你  待會兒打給你  好嗎
Okay. I love you. I'll talk to you soon, all right?
別擔心  再見
Don't worry. Okay, bye.
星期五
下午5:23
她知道你是做什麼的嗎
She know what you do for a living?
電話裡那個女孩  是女的吧
The girl on the phone. It was a girl, wasn't it?
也許是男的  我不知道
Maybe it was a guy, I don't know.
我不做評論
I don't judge.
你得知道
You can't expect to have a
做我們這行的不能動心  馬特
real relationship in our line of work, Matthew.
別擔心  她不會離開你的
Don't worry. She's not going to leave you.
但是  你試圖用謊言保護她
See, what happens is, you try to protect her with lies,
最後越來越多
and then it starts to add up.
在安全屋你說他們會為了抓你而殺了我
At the safe house you said that they'd kill me to get to you.
等過段時間  就連真相
After a while, even the truth. . .
-怎麼了  -聽起來也像謊言
- Why?...- Starts to sound like a lie.
你有件東西  他們想要的  是什麼
You have something. You got something that they want. What is it?
她是本地人嗎
Is she a local?
別管她  是什麼
Don't worry about her. What is it?
是女孩兒啊
Oh, it is a girl.
你會一直說謊  而她會一直相信你
You'll keep covering your tracks, she'll keep believing.
因為她想相信  她需要相信
Because she wants to, because she needs to.
這就是我們存在的理由  你和我  我們的工作
That's why we exist, you and me, that's our job.
利用別人這一點
To take advantage of that.
人們渴望相信
People's desire to believe.
渴望信任
To trust.
她不會離開你的  馬特
She's not going to leave you, Matthew.
你會離開她
You're going to leave her.
我不是你
I'm not you.
沒錯  長官  已經確認了
Correct, sir. We verified it.
那是你的人  你處理
That is your boy. You take it.
所有人準備
Everybody, stand by.
馬特  是我
Matty, it's me.
你怎麼樣
How are you holding up?
我還好
I'm all right.
馬特  支援至少要等12小時
Matt, we can't get another team in for at least 12 hours.
抱歉
Sorry.
我們在城外幫你準備了另一個安全屋
We've cleared a new safe house for you outside the city.
有一個應急包
There's a Go-Bag located
在綠點體育館地鐵站  256號櫃子裡
at locker number 256, Green Point Stadium Metrorail station.
密碼是  2-5-1-22
The combination is 2-5-1-22.
2-5-1-22
2-5-1-22.
包裡有衛星定位器
Now, the bag's got a GPS in it.
它會把你帶去新安全屋
It'll direct you to the safe house.
但是你要小心  那附近很亂
But you got to be careful, it's an active location.
要小心行事
So, approach with caution.
馬特
Matt?
你知道他們怎麼找到福斯特的嗎
Do you know how they found Frost?
你知道是誰把他們帶去的嗎
Do you know who led them to us?
我們正在調查
We're working on that.
全靠你了  馬特
We're counting on you, Matt.
把福斯特帶到那裡  然後你就自由了
Get Frost to that safe house and you can write your own ticket.
我知道了
I will.
左邊燈那裡
Left at the light.
去體育館嗎
To the stadium?
是的
Yeah.
買圍巾的  一條圍巾多少錢
Hey, scarf. How much for a scarf?
只要50蘭特
Only fifty Rand.
謝謝
Thanks.
把手銬起來
Cuff your hands together.
-銬一起  -對
- Together? - Yeah.
下來
Out.
你確定你不想一走了之嗎
Are you sure you don't want to just walk away from this?
做不到
Can't do that.
做得到  你應該如此
Yes, you can. You should.
走  過街
Move. Go. Across the street.
去看比賽  我喜歡比賽
Going to the game. I like games.
地鐵站  直走
Metrorail, straight ahead.
直走
Straight ahead.
去那裡
Right over there.
我們走
Let's go.
救命  救命  他想綁架我
Help! Help! He's trying to kidnap me!
他要綁架我  救命
He's trying to kidnap me! Help!
他身上有槍
He's got a gun !
我是臥底  我是員警
他有槍  就在那
He's got a gun ! He's got a gun right there!
我是臥底  我是臥底
I'm undercover. I'm undercover!
冷靜  所有人  冷靜下來
Calm down, sir. Everybody, calm down !
趴下  趴下
Get down ! Get down !
好的  好的
All right! Okay!
我逮捕了他  他是殺人犯
扶他起來  起來
Get him up. Get up.
我是美國公民  我不知道他想幹什麼
I'm an American citizen. I don't know what he wanted from me.
冷靜一下
Just calm down.
你們不明白  他非常危險
我是員警  美國來的
Hey, hey, hey. I'm a police officer. I'm from America.
我逮捕了他  他叫托賓·福斯特
I arrested this man. His name is Tobin Frost.
你把他帶去哪了
Where did you take him?
他在醫務室
He's in the infirmary.
那裡  是那嗎
There, there! Is that it?
左上角  第二排  快看  醫務室
Top left, second screen from the top! Look, look, the infirmary.
倒回去一點
Right. Go back.
第三層醫務室  行動
Third-tier infirmary, now! Move!
Third-tier infirmary. Go, now!
你沒看見嗎
Do you see?
不許動
Don't move.
發現嫌犯  看臺上層西南面
注意下層廣場
發現嫌犯經過黃區228號
福斯特
Frost!
站住  站住
Stop! Stop!
讓開
Get out the way!
站住
Stop!
不  站住
No! Stop!
醫生
Medic!
把槍放下
Drop the gun.
放下
Drop it.
我要對你負責
I'm responsible for you.
你對自己負責就行
You're responsible for yourself.
跪下
Get on your knees.
你要殺我嗎
Are you going to kill me?
我只殺專業人士
I only kill professionals.
身高大約6英尺
Height, approximateIy six feet.
星期五
晚上7:53
白人  身穿體育館保安制服
Anglo, wearing a stadium security jacket.
嫌犯最後被目擊進入綠點體育場地鐵站
The suspect was last seen entering Green Point Stadium Metrorail,
體育館大廳
stadium concourse.
長官  有福斯特現身開普敦的線索
Sir, we have a thread on what Frost might be doing in Cape Town.
你能把它
Can you bring up. . .
阿列克·韋德  當了15年軍情六處的臥底
Alec Wade. Fifteen-year NOC at MI6.
參與過破壞  反狙擊  反簡易爆炸等行動
Sabotage, counter-ambush, counter-IED tactics,
直到他4年前在里斯本搞砸了一項行動
until he blew up an op in Lisbon four years ago
後被轉職做文件工作
and was put on a desk, pushing papers.
開普敦警方發現他頭部中槍
Cape Town Police found him shot through the head,
用的是強力來福槍  距領事館14個街區
high-powered rifle, 14 blocks from the consulate.
目擊者對車內另一人的描述
Witnesses placed someone fitting Frost's description
符合福斯特的特徵
in the car at the time of the shooting.
所以結論是什麼  他們有合作嗎
And we think, what? That they were working together?
他們80年代就在漢堡合作過
They ran joint operations in Hamburg in the mid-'80s.
福斯特最後也是2011年在漢堡出現的
Frost's last sighting was in Hamburg, 2011.
英國人對韋德有什麼說法
And what are the Brits saying about Wade?
官方他們什麼都沒說
Officially, they're saying nothing.
非官方呢
Unofficially?
他是五個月以來內部調查的目標
He's been the subject of a five-month internal investigation.
他們認為他在出售情報
They think he's been trading intel.
那麼韋德賣了什麼重要情報給福斯特
So what the hell did Wade leak to Frost
竟然害死我們6個人
that was so important it was worth killing six of our men?
向軍情六處瞭解詳情  聯繫所有管道
I want more details from MI6. Call in every chit you got.
是  長官
Yes, sir.
大衛  我要進行內部調查
David, I want an internal investigation
調查丹尼爾·季福爾和他的隊伍
into Daniel Kiefer and his team.
韋斯頓來電找大衛·巴羅
I've got Weston calling in for David Barlow.
我把他弄丟了
I lost him.
福斯特嗎
Frost?
是的  他跑了
Yeah, he's gone.
我拿到定位系統後  他製造混亂
After I picked up the GPS, he created a diversion,
殺了體育館兩個員警
took out a couple of cops at the stadium.
他可能去哪
Any idea where he's headed?
不清楚  但我會盡力找
Not exactly, but I will.
我是林克雷特  你說他殺了兩個員警
This is Linklater. You said he took out two cops?
馬特  接到免提上了
Matt, you're on speaker.
是的  長官  在綠點體育館
Yes, ma'am. At the Green Point Stadium.
可能涉嫌綁架
...involvement in a possible kidnapping.
據描述  嫌疑人為中等身材白人
The suspect is being described as a white male of medium build.
體育館警方說你殺了一個員警
Stadium police is reporting you shot a cop.
我開槍是為了自衛
I returned fire in self-defense.
重點是  福斯特跑了
The fact of the matter is, Frost is on the loose.
我前面14個小時都和他在一起
I've spent the last 14 hours with him.
他說的或者做的可能幫我找到他
He might have said or done something that could lead me to him.
你撤退  前往領事館
You are to stand down, proceed to the consulate,
表明自己是撤退來彙報情況的  請確認
and present yourself for exfil and debrief. Acknowledge.
等我彙報完情況  福斯特就找不到了
By the time I'm debriefed, Frost will be gone.
我花了12個月瞭解
I've spent 12 months researching
這城市每一寸土地
every square inch of this town.
我會找到福斯特把他送來的
I will find Frost and I'll deliver him.
韋斯頓  我是哈倫·魏特福
Weston, this is Harlan Whitford, son.
你做得很好  現在我們接手了
Now, you've done a fine job, but we'll take it from here.
明白
Understood.
喂
Hello.
長官  我提議
Sir, I respectfully request that,
這次交接不要寫入他的檔案
that exchange not make it onto his files.
他要麼是無能  要麼就是跟人合謀
He's either incompetent or he's working with somebody else.
別這麼說韋斯頓
Do not make this about Weston.
你的人丟了福斯特
It was your guys that lost Frost.
你的隊伍毀了安全屋
It was your team that folded at the safe house.
你們倆飛去開普敦
I want both of you on an airplane to Cape Town.
福斯特想逃離南非  找到他
Frost is trying to get out of the country. Go find his ass.
星期五
晚上8:37
出來了  寶貝兒
There you go, baby.
一張去約翰尼斯堡的票
One ticket to Jo'burg.
謝謝
Thank you.
警方已拘留非政府工作人員馬特·韋斯頓
Police had detained American NGO worker Matthew Weston
作為槍擊事件嫌疑犯
as a possible suspect in the shooting.
韋斯頓今日早些時候被拘留
Weston had been detained earlier today,
但卻在被體育館保安詢問槍擊事件時
but managed to escape while being questioned by stadium security officials
設法逃脫
about his involvement in the shootings.
嫌疑犯是中等身材的白人男性
The suspect has been described as a white male of medium build,
可能身穿體育館保安制服
possibly wearing a stadium security outfit.
寶貝
Baby.
你還好嗎
Are you all right?
我欺騙了你
l lied to you.
關於所有事  非政府工作  派克
About everything. The NGO, Parker.
還有我的工作
My job.
我的家庭
My family.
那麼你是為誰工作的
So, who do you work for?
政府
The government.
美國中情局
CIA.
不  我不是
No, I don't. . .
我不用做任何事
I don't do anything.
我整天坐在公寓裡  接電話
I sit around in an apartment all day. I answer the phone.
我需要你離開
I need you to leave.
你能為我做這一件事嗎
I need you to do that for me. Okay?
給你
Here.
這是去約翰尼斯堡的機票
This is a ticket to Jo'burg.
你到了之後  直接去機場
When you get there, you go straight to the airport.
有一班早上6點的航班去巴黎
There's a 6:00 A.M. Flight to Paris.
拿好
Take this.
你拿著這個  如果有任何人阻止你
You take this. If anyone stops you. . .
如果有任何人阻止你  有任何人阻止你
If anyone stops you. . . If anybody stops you. . .
你以為我是誰
Who do you think I am?
停下  停下
Stop, stop.
去你媽的
Fuck you!
別這樣  停下
Hey, stop. Stop it.
我們一周前分手了  之後你都沒見過我  好嗎
We broke up a week ago. You haven't seen me since, okay?
對不起
I'm sorry.
快走吧  求你了
Just leave. Please?
你愛我嗎
Do you love me?
非常愛
Very much.
走吧
Go. Go.
走啊
Go.
各位乘客請注意
Attention, all passengers,
20號月臺開往朗加的火車
Platform 20 for Langa Township
將在5分鐘後出發
departing in five minutes.
朗加  5分鐘後啟程
Langa Township, departing in five minutes.
南非監視分析系統
長官  有人用韋斯頓的密碼登陸系統
Sir. Someone just logged into our system using Weston's password
訪問他存儲的資料
accessing his stored files.
盜用馬特·韋斯頓帳戶登入
是他  他想幹嘛
It's him. What the hell is he doing?
不清楚
I'm not sure.
看看他看的東西
I want to see what he's looking at.
他在查看一份關於
He's pulled an old report
住在郎加的被監視者的舊報告
on surveillance targets living in the Langa Township area.
一個尼加拉瓜人
It's a profile of Carlos Villar,
卡洛斯·維勒的檔案
a Nicaraguan national.
他是有名的證件造假者
He's a known document forger.
卡洛斯·維勒的地址
給我拷貝一份韋斯頓的報告
Get me a copy of Weston's report.
是的  長官
Yes, sir.
登出了  長官  他走了
Logged off, sir. He's gone.
在長街的一個網吧
An Internet cafe on Long Street.
長街  開普敦的酒吧一條街
開普敦  郎加
風采不減當年啊
Like a black Dorian Gray.
那就對了  怎麼樣了  兄弟
That's right. How you doing, brother?
-進來  -是
- Come in. - Yes, sir.
伊拉娜
Illana?
有客人來了  我的老同事
We have a guest. My old colleague.
伊拉娜  很高興見到你
Illana. Good to meet you.
約瑟芬  我女兒
Joseph, my daughter.
-你好嗎  -你好
- How are you? - Hello.
我女婿
My son-in-law.
給你倒點茶吧
May I offer you some tea?
不  我們上樓去
No, we're going upstairs.
我們要談點工作上的事
We have something to discuss, about business.
危險嗎
Is it dangerous?
不  別擔心
No, don't worry.
我記得你愛喝它
I remembered.
你甚至要讓它呼吸
You even let it breathe.
犧牲太久  心都變硬了
Too long a sacrifice can make a stone of the heart.
什麼時候才會滿足
Or when may it suffice?
可能到了天堂吧
That is Heaven's part.
過去  一瓶便宜的弗洛爾塔卡納
In the old days, a cheap bottle
弗洛爾塔卡納  尼加拉瓜的一種朗姆酒
就夠咱倆高興一整晚
of Flor de Cana kept us happy all night.
是啊  口味變了
Mmm. Tastes change.
人變了
People change.
人沒變
People don't change.
只是老了
We grow old.
一些人適應了
And some of us adapt.
學著如何享受生活的平淡樂趣
And learn how to enjoy simple pleasures of life,
比如親人  家庭
like a family, a home.
對你而言
And for you...
現在瓶中的東西  對你而言
What's in that glass right now, for you,
還跟以前一樣好
is as good as it's ever going to be.
總有一天你會懂的
One day you'll understand.
你對過去掛念太多
You got more past than future,
得學著走出來
you learn.
這是什麼意思  勸我嗎
What is this? An intervention?
我以為你死了
I thought you were dead.
所以  這麼多年後
So, what brings you to my home
什麼風把你半夜吹到我家來了
in the middle of the night after all these years?
爸爸
Papa?
我們出去了
We're going.
所有資料已經驗證
好的  小心點
Okay, be careful.
好的  爸爸
Okay, Papa.
美英德等多國情報機構貪污詳情
你準備拿這個怎麼辦
What are you going to do with this?
賺些錢
Make some money.
眼鏡借我用下
Let me borrow your glasses.
就是這個  聽著
That's it. Listen.
我需要一個新的護照
I'm going to need a new passport,
帶照片的身份證  駕照
photo ID, driver's license,
一整套新的  你能幫我做到嗎
the whole shebang. Can you do that for me?
是的
Yeah.
你確定
You sure?
對
Yes.
韋斯頓從沒在領事館露過面
Weston never showed at the consulate.
他剛進入了我們的安全伺服器
And he was just accessing our secure server,
找人辦假證件
searching for someone to create an alias package.
他想離開這個國家
He's trying to leave the country.
或者他在追福斯特
Or he's going after Frost.
看看在足球賽體育場發生了什麼
Look at what happened at the soccer stadium.
這傢伙讓福斯特跑了
This guy let Frost escape.
我覺得韋斯頓叛變了
I think Weston's turned.
我瞭解這孩子
I know this boy.
他一直在找機會證明自己
He's been looking for a chance to prove himself.
他想把福斯特帶過來
He's trying to bring in Frost.
少來了  大衛
Come on, David.
你並沒看到證據
You're not seeing the evidence.
美國護照
不夠好
Not my best work.
但在時間緊迫的情況下
But given the pressure of time,
還算過得去
it's passable.
很好  我一出城
It's good. I'll wire you the money
就把錢郵給你
as soon as I get out of town.
托賓  別這樣  這不一樣
Tobin, don't do this. It's different.
不用麻煩  不用寄錢
You don't need the trouble, you don't need the money.
你可以把它給...
You can give it...
卡洛斯
Carlos!
伊拉娜
Illana!
卡洛斯
Carlos!
伊拉娜
Illana!
卡洛斯
Carlos.
Carlos!
走
Go.
去那兒  走
Right there. Go!
他在房頂上
He's on the roof!
跟上他
After him!
走  走
Go! Go!
上車
Get in the car!
他們覺得可以這樣來找我
They think they can come at me like this.
我本該做得遠比現在更好
Have to do it a whole lot better than that.
該死
Shit!
馬特  你怎麼找到我的
Matt, how'd you find me?
沒那麼難
It wasn't that hard.
我們走
Let's go.
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait.
你為誰做事
Who do you work for?
誰派你來的  誰派你來的
Who sent you? Who sent you?
誰
Who?
瓦加斯
Vargas.
-誰  -瓦加斯
- Who? - Vargas.
誰是瓦加斯
Who's Vargas?
你想死嗎
You want to die?
誰是瓦加斯
Who's Vargas?
馬特
Matt.
中情局
CIA.
中情局  中情局
CIA! CIA!
星期六
早上6:17
報告
Report?
郎加發生一起槍戰
There was a shootout in the Langa Township.
兩處犯罪現場
Two crime scenes.
一處在卡洛斯·維勒的住所
One at the residence of Carlos Villar.
他是證件造假者
He's a document forger.
另一處在附近的公寓
The other in a nearby tenement.
最後看到福斯特的地方是哪
And where was Frost last seen?
公寓
Tenement.
祝你在維勒家有所收穫
Have fun at Villar's.
一會兒見
We'll meet up later.
屈倫博赫藥房
關於安娜你是對的
You were right about Ana.
那是她的名字
That's her name.
抱歉聽到這個
Sorry to hear that.
大多數情報官員都結三到四次婚
Most case officers get married three, four times.
你呢
You?
一次
Once.
你這裡的繃帶鬆開了
You're falling apart over here.
別殺無辜的人  馬特
Don't kill innocent people, Matthew.
什麼
What?
有個空中交管員
Air traffic controller,
管理百慕大群島的一個小跑道
a tiny airstrip in Bermuda.
喬治·愛德華特·考克斯  我記得那個名字
George Edwart Cox, I remember that name.
愛德華特  有個特
Edwart, with a T.
組織說他在運送武器
My inside officer said he was organizing arms shipments,
但他只是個空中交管員
but he was just an air traffic controller.
老百姓一名
He was just a guy.
我朝他的頭開了一槍
I put a bullet in his skull.
之後特警們插手
Black Ops came in,
其中一人接替了他
they replaced him with one of their own,
結果有艘飛機在那晚由於灣流墜入海底
and crashed a Gulfstream in the ocean that night.
事實是  在飛機上的那家人
The thing was, the family that was on the plane...
那個丈夫  是個告密者
The husband, he was a whistleblower.
這整件事就是要
The whole thing was about
阻止他向國會聽證會
stopping him from testifying about wet work
告發這次謀殺行動
to a congressional hearing.
那就是你離開的原因
Is that why you left?
不
No.
我第二天
I went back to work the next day
就像什麼都沒發生一樣回去工作
like nothing ever happened.
熟能生巧
You practice anything a long time, you get good at it.
謊說得多了  就像真的一樣
You tell a hundred lies a day, it sounds like the truth.
人們彼此背叛
Everyone betrays everyone.
那是個糟糕的藉口
That's a shitty excuse.
是的  我曾經像你一樣天真
Yeah, I used to be innocent like you.
為國效力
Wrap myself up in the flag...
我要帶你過去
I'm going to take you in.
好樣的
Good for you.
巴羅
Barlow.
目擊者證實兩名
Witnesses identified a pair of men
符合韋斯頓和福斯特特徵的男人
fitting weston and Frost's description
一起離開了這裡
leaving this location together.
所以  他成功了
So, he pulled it off.
韋斯頓協助並教唆逃犯
Weston is aiding and abetting a fugitive.
你錯了
You're wrong.
如果他跟福斯特在一起
If he's with Frost,
一定正帶他去安全屋
he's taking him to the safe house.
我們該去那兒
That's where we got to be.
好吧  好吧
Fine. Fine.
在老馬姆斯伯裡路的岔路口見
Meet me at the crossroads at Old Malmesbury Road.
星期六
上午11:43
你是誰
Who are you?
韋斯頓嗎
You Weston?
把槍給我
Give me the shotgun.
這是怎麼回事
What the hell is this?
你是誰
Who are you?
我是凱勒  安全屋看守
l'm Keller. Safe house keeper.
身份確定
Authorization lndex,
編號B47OW6
Bravo Four Seven Oscar Whiskey Six.
進來  我們走
lnside. Let's go.
左邊
To the left.
慢點
Slowly.
兄弟   我不知道誰培訓的你
I don't know who trained you, man, but this sure as hell
但法則肯定不是這樣的
ain't protocol.
客房在哪
Where's the guest room?
就是那個  我們並沒有客房
That's the thing, we don't really have one.
進那裡去  進那裡去
In there. In there.
把他銬到管子上
Cuff him. To the pipe.
出來  那裡
Out. Over there.
好吧
All right.
控制室
Control room.
聽你的  夥計  你來掌控
Whatever you say, man. It's your rodeo.
打電話進去  讓我聽到
Call it in. Let me hear it.
我是房東
LandLord.
我的客人在這兒
My guest is here.
預約用戶名?
Account?
阿拉貝斯克有限公司
Abaresque Limited.
客人來了嗎
with a guest?
是的  包裹已送到
Yeah, package delivered.
確認  按計劃接收
Confirmed. Pickup scheduled.
他們在路上了
They're on the way.
現在至少能放下槍了吧
Can we at least put the gun down now?
謝謝  克萊頓  再見
Thanks, Clayton. Bye.
它是微晶片
It's a microchip.
什麼
What?
我中情六處的夥計說的
That was my guy from MI6.
韋德拿到了微晶片
Wade got his hands on a microchip.
上面有什麼
And what was on it?
只有韋德知道
Only Wade knew,
這樣他跟福斯特碰頭的原因
but I think it's safe to assume
就說得通了
that's why he hooked up with Frost.
為了賣掉它
To sell it.
我們走吧
Let's get moving.
漫長的一天  是吧
Long day, huh?
我只能想像  托賓·福斯特
I can only imagine. Tobin Frost.
他是傳奇啊
That man's a legend.
我希望你學到了一些
I hope you picked up something.
你可找不到更好的學習物件了
You ain't going to find a better education.
這是我見過的最刺激的
This is the most excitement I've seen.
你是10個月以來第一位客人
You're the first guest I've had in 10 months.
但你什麼都不知道 是嗎
But you wouldn't know anything about that, right?
你有整個城市
You got a city posting.
是啊  夜生活  海灘
Yeah, nightlife, beaches.
到處跑的小妞兒
Little ladies running around everywhere.
是啊
Yeah.
我嫉妒了
I'm jealous.
有咖啡嗎
You got coffee?
有  在壁櫥裡
Yeah, it's in the cupboard.
哪裡
Where?
-要我拿嗎  -我來
- Want me to get it? - I got it.
為什麼你  為什麼你會在開普敦
Why you... Why are you in Cape Town?
現在告訴我  為什麼
Tell me now. Why?
它是什麼
What is it?
骯髒的名單  很長的名單
A dirt list, laundry list.
五年前  以色列情報局
lsraeli lntelligence, five years ago,
編輯的勒索情報
compiled blackmail intel.
腐敗的特工  德國情報局  軍情六處
Corrupt agents, German lntelligence, Ml6...
還有中情局?
CIA?
對
Yes.
我們得離開
We got to get away.
我們得離開這兒
We got to get out of here.
該死
Ah, shit.
不要  不要  不要
Don't, don't, don't, don't.
不要  不  不要
Don't. No, don't,
別留我在這兒  求你了
don't leave me here, please.
別  別這麼做
Don't, Don't do it.
馬特
Matt?
你好
Hey.
怎麼樣了
How you doing?
我為你驕傲
I'm proud of you.
為你做成的事驕傲
And what you pulled off.
你會成為出色的情報官員
You're going to make a hell of a case officer.
福斯特在哪
Where's Frost?
他走了
He's gone.
這地方毀了  到處是血
Place is a wreck. Blood everywhere.
他受傷了還是
Was he injured or...
我猜你知道他殺了凱勒
I guess you know he killed Keller.
不
No.
我殺了凱勒
I killed Keller.
福斯特殺了凱勒
Frost killed Keller.
他也殺了林克雷特
He killed Linklater, too.
他說過什麼嗎
Did he talk about anything?
他在找什麼
Anything he was after?
他可能有什麼
Anything he might have had?
文件
The file.
The file?
有你在上面的那個檔
The file that you're on.
還有很多其他人
Along with a lot of other people.
重要人物
Important people.
聽我說
Listen to me.
要是有人監視你的
What would you do
一舉一動的話你會怎麼做
if someone is watching your every move?
不那麼光彩的事
Some maybe you're not proud of.
你也會有不光彩的事的  相信我
And you will have some you're not proud of, believe me.
然後試圖用它來對付你
And then tries to use it against you?
你就逼不得已了
You would do what you have to do.
文件在哪
Where's the file?
馬特  文件  文件在哪
Matt, the file. Where is the file?
你已經死了
You're a dead man.
是啊  死了很久了
Yeah, a long time now.
福斯特在這兒
Frost is here.
我們走
Let's go.
我們抓住他了
We got him.
幹得漂亮
A hell of a job.
你聞到沒
You smell that?
品樂塔吉  好葡萄  好酒
Pinotage. It's a good grape. Great wine.
當地的葡萄  品樂塔吉太棒了
Local grape. Pinotage is great...
品樂塔吉  是南非自己培育的  最有名的釀酒葡萄品種
我不想你把這個弄丟
I don't want you losing this one.
它值很多錢
It's worth a lot of money.
你是個好孩子  馬特
You're a good boy, Matty.
你知道你是什麼人
You know what you are.
我知道你不是什麼人
I know what you're not.
你比我好
You're better than me.
不  沒事  比我好就可以了
No, it's okay, just be better than me.
跟我保證
You promise me.
好
Yeah.
我們  我們
Well, let's... let's
我們走
Let's go.
我只是得起來  我要起來
I just got to get up. I need to get up.
別動
Stay.
維吉尼亞州蘭利  中情局總部
一切據實所述
That's exactly as it happened.
顯然  這種情況需要
Obviously, this situation needs
用一些特殊手段來處理
to be handled with a certain amount of finesse.
還有其他人看過這份報告嗎
Has anybody else seen this report?
沒有  長官  還沒
No, sir. Not yet.
馬特  我確定這些都真實無疑
Matt, I'm sure this comes as no surprise,
但是這個報告的一些部分
but parts of this report are
將會威脅到國家安全
going to have to be altered for national security.
哪些部分  長官
Which parts, sir?
大衛·巴羅不能為
Well... David Barlow can't be held responsible
安全屋事件負責
for what happened to the safe house.
我們不需要這個醜聞
We just don't need the scandal.
但是  長官  我們都知道
But, sir, you and I both know that,
那不是事實
that is just not the truth.
人們不再需要事實了  馬特
People don't want the truth anymore, Matt.
它太麻煩了  把它們永遠埋葬吧
It's too messy. Keeps them up nights.
但我會告訴你我準備做什麼
I'll tell you what I am willing to do, though.
我覺得局裡太低估你了
I think the Agency has grossly underestimated you,
我推薦給你一個
and I'm recommending you
更高的情報官員的職位
for a senior case officer position.
請表示你還想要它
Provided you still want it.
這是個慷慨的給予  長官
That's a generous offer, sir.
你只需為我澄清一件事
There's just one thing you need to clarify for me.
當然
Of course.
福斯特曾帶著一些重要的情報
Frost may have been carrying some vital intel.
一份文件
A file.
我沒在這報告的任何地方看到它
I'm not seeing that anywhere in this report.
檔裡有什麼  長官
What was on the file, sir?
坦白說  一些對局裡和我們的盟友
Something that, quite frankly, could be very damaging
很有毀滅性的東西
to the Agency and to our allies.
我不明白為什麼
I don't see why Frost
福斯特會跟我說那樣的事
would even mention something like that to me.
對  我覺得他不會  是嗎
No, I suppose he wouldn't, would he?
但是你知道  如果那份檔洩露出去
You realize, though, that if that file did leak,
相關人員會怎樣嗎
what would happen to the person responsible?
那些人會被逮捕  長官
That person would be arrested, sir.
他賭上了全部
He'd be risking everything.
他會在全世界
He'd have enemies
所有情報局樹敵
in every intelligence agency in the world.
對中情局來說
In the eyes of the CIA,
他會跟托賓·福斯特一樣
he'd be just like Tobin Frost.
福斯特沒說任何
Frost didn't say anything
關於檔的事  長官
about a file, sir.
好吧  孩子
All right, son.
休息幾天
Take a few days off.
下周讓你開始工作
We'll get you started next week.
謝謝你
Thank you.
想想我們的談話  好嗎
And think about our conversation, would you?
我會的
Will do.
剩下的我來處理  長官
I'll take it from here, sir.
美國中央情報局
郵件發送中
其他媒體透露
and other media outlets
他們從未知源接收到有爭議性的文件
received a controversial file from an anonymous source.
國際情報組織仍在為
The international intelligence community is still reeling
美國有線電視新聞網  新聞直播間  情報局洩露事件
如此高機密情報的洩露
from the release of so many highly classified documents
以及中情局 德國聯邦情報局
and the revelations of
和軍情六處的普遍的腐敗和犯罪活動
widespread corruption and criminal activity
感到震驚不已
at the CIA, the BND, and MI6.
英國有線新聞  國會控告軍情六處官員
由於英國情報局的疏忽
is in an uproar over the lack
引起軒然大波
of oversight given to British Intelligence,
要求涉案特工承擔後果
demanding accountability of the rogue agents.
軍情六處的官員正在全力合作
Officials at MI6 are fully cooperating.
德國有線新聞  德國聯邦情報局陷身醜聞
默克爾總理堅稱德國聯邦情報局
Chancellor Merkel insists that the BND
已確認了腐敗特工
has already identified the corrupt agents
控制了情報洩露
and contained the intelligence breach.
她確認了她的國際同仁
She has ensured her international counterparts...
美國有線電視新聞網  新聞直播間  情報局洩露事件
起訴有望在本周進行
Indictments are now expected within the week,
國會已要求副局長哈倫·魏特福
and Congress has demanded that Deputy Director Harlan Whitford
在參議院附屬委員會面前證明
testify before a Senate subcommittee
中情局中有多少人
in an effort to determine how many people
涉及此案
at the CIA are involved in this
以及腐敗的範圍
and just how far up the corruption reaches.
法國  巴黎
可悲的人類  已變成暴徒
Human beings in a mob
暴徒算什麼  對國王而言
What's a mob to a king
國王算什麼  對上帝而言
What's a king to a god
上帝算什麼  對無信仰者而言
What's a god to a non-believer
怎麼會有人  不信任何事
Who don't believe in anything
我們頑強地  堅持活下去
We make it out alive
好吧  好吧
All right, all right
曠野之上沒有教堂
No church in the wild
眼淚滴落在  陵墓的地板
Tears on the mausoleum floor
血液飛濺在  體育館門上
Blood stains the coliseum doors
神父的嘴上  編造著謊言
Lies of the lips of a priest
感恩的節日  偽裝成盛宴
Thanksgiving disguised as a feast
駕駛著豪車  在海邊賓士
Rolling in the Rolls-Royce Corniche
醫生的享受  而我在躲避
Only the doctors got this, I'm hiding from police
座下藏毒品
Cocaine seats
所有白人們  都能被寬恕
All white like I got the whole thing bleached
毒販們
Drug dealer chic
和平的禱告  是否能到達
I'm wondering if a dove's prayers reach
虔誠的庇護  上帝愛保護
It's pious Pius, the god loves Pius
蘇格拉底問  尋求誰的愛
Socrates asks, 'Whose bias do y'all seek?'
或是柏拉圖  揪心地尖叫
Or for Plato, the screech
偷溜到外面  你已經聽到
I'm out there ballin', I know you hear my sneaks
耶穌是木匠  他懂得鼓點
Jesus was a carpenter, Yeezy, he lay beats
霍流聖靈啊  滾出座位去
Hova flow the Holy Ghost, get the hell up out your seats
講道啊
Preach
可悲的人類  已變成暴徒
Human beings in a mob
暴徒算什麼  對國王而言
What's a mob to a king
國王算什麼  對上帝而言
What's a king to a god?
上帝算什麼  對無信仰者而言
What's a god to a non-believer
怎麼會有人  不信任何事
Who don't believe in anything
我們頑強地  堅持活下去
We make it out alive
好吧  好吧
All right, all right
曠野之上沒有教堂
No church in the wild
讓我來給你
Let me buy you
心中的渴望
Desire
我在你身旁
I stand by you
共走過火焰
Walk through the fire
而你的生命
Your life
是我的聖經
Is my Scripture
我真需要它
And I need it
通過你加密
Through your encryption
她的黑皮膚  斑馬狀條紋
Coke on her black skin made a stripe like a zebra
我把那叫做  叢林的狂熱
I call that jungle fever
三人行種種  你沒法掌控
You will not control the threesome
努力地做吧  直到有快感
Just roll the weed up until I get me some
已然形成了  全新的宗教
We formed a new religion
若沒有允許  就沒有罪惡
No sins as long as there's permission
只剩下欺騙  唯一的重罪
And deception is the only felony
若沒有告我  不可以做愛
So never fuck anybody with out telling me
太陽鏡和止痛藥
Sunglasses and Advil
昨晚一整晚  瘋狂無底線
Last night was mad real
太陽如往常  早早地升起
Sun coming up, 5 a.m.
渾身已無力  怎麼回家去
I wonder if they got cabs still
想著利物浦  美麗的姑娘
Thinking about the girl in all-leopard
有誰能跟我  一起玩樂去
Who was rubbing the wood like Kiki Shepard
有兩個紋身  一說無歉意
Two tattooers, one read 'No Apologies'
另說愛情被  忠貞所詛咒
The other said 'Love is cursed by monogamy'
牧師講道中  不會說這些
That's something that the pastor don't preach
老師上課時  也不講這些
That's something that a teacher can't teach
當我們死去  財寶帶不走
When we die, the money we can't keep
可能全花光  疼痛不便宜
But we probably spend it all cause the pain ain't cheap
講道啊
Preach
可悲的人類  已變成暴徒
Human beings in a mob
暴徒算什麼  對國王而言
What's a mob to a king
國王算什麼  對上帝而言
What's a king to a god
上帝算什麼  對無信仰者而言
What's a god to a non-believer
怎麼會有人  不信任何事
Who don't believe in anything
我們頑強地  堅持活下去
We make it out alive
好吧  好吧
All right, all right
曠野之上沒有教堂
No church in the wild